[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This fictional koala character, created by author Dorothy Wall, fist appeared in the 1933 book Jacko - the Broadcasting Kookaburra.", "correct_answer": "Blinky Bill", "incorrect_answers": ["Nutsy", "Jeremy", "Noozles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the winner of the 1994 Razzie Award for Worst Picture.", "correct_answer": "Color of Night", "incorrect_answers": ["Wyatt Earp", "On Deadly Ground", "The Specialist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the destiny (not goal) of Damien Thorn in the 1976 movie The Omen?", "correct_answer": "To become the Antichrist", "incorrect_answers": ["To find the fountain of youth", "To invent a medicine that prolongs human life", "To become President of the united States"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Pretty in Pink, Duckie is Andies boyfriend.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Andy Dufresne escape in the movie The Shawshank Redemption?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Ohio River does not flow though the territory of this American state.", "correct_answer": "Virginia", "incorrect_answers": ["Illinois", "Kentucky", "West Virginia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the birth name of singer Johnny Cash, whose life is depicted in the movie Walk the Line?", "correct_answer": "J. R. Cash", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnny Cash", "John Randall Cash", "John Cash Jr."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other name is commonly used for the wolfberry?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Mede berry", "Goji berry", "Barbary matrimony vine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Sin City, what clothing item does Marv admire on one of the bounty hunters that try to catch him?", "correct_answer": "a coat", "incorrect_answers": ["a hat", "a pair of blue swede shoes", "a belt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Egyptian territory is calculated to be roughly twice as large as the territory of this European country.", "correct_answer": "Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["Poland", "France", "United Kingdom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the special magic power of the philosophers stone that alchemists were searching for?", "correct_answer": "It would give them unprecedented knowledge.", "incorrect_answers": ["It would bring them luck and happiness.", "It would grant them eternal life.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors has not appeared in three or more Mel Brooks films?", "correct_answer": "Cleavon Little", "incorrect_answers": ["Gene Wilder", "Madeline Kahn", "Dom Deluise"]}]